Welcome to the day after judgement day
Terminator: Dark Fate is a science fiction, action,
adventure film directed by Tim Miller.
Decades after Sarah Connor prevented Judgment Day, a lethal new Terminator
is sent to eliminate the future leader of the resistance.
In a fight to save mankind, battle-hardened Sarah Connor teams up with an unexpected
ally and an enhanced super soldier to stop the deadliest Terminator yet.
Sarah Connor, played by Linda Hamilton.
T-800 / Carl, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Grace, played by Mackenzie Davis.
Daniella "Dani" Ramos, played by Natalia Reyes.
Gabriel / REV-9, played by Gabriel Luna.
Diego Ramos, played by Diego Boneta.
Terminator: Dark Fate is a 2019 American science
fiction action film directed by Tim Miller.
It is the sixth film in the Terminator franchise and a direct sequel to Terminator 2:
Judgment Day (1991), ignoring the events of the intervening sequels.
The film was written by David S.
Goyer, Justin Rhodes, and Billy Ray.
The film stars Linda Hamilton and Arnold Schwarzenegger reprising their roles as Sarah Connor and
the Terminator respectively, and also features Mackenzie Davis and Natalia Reyes.
The film is set 25 years after the events of Terminator 2, when a malevolent artificial intelligence known as Legion from an alternate future, sends a highly advanced
Terminator, the Rev-9, back in time to 2020 with instructions to kill Dani Ramos, whose fate is to become the leader of the Human Resistance in the future.
The Resistance also sends Grace, an augmented soldier, back in time to defend Dani,
who is also joined by Sarah Connor and Skynet's T-800 Terminator.
Principal photography took place from June to November 2018
in Hungary, Spain, and the United States.
The film was released theatrically in the United States on
November 1, 2019, by Paramount Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and grossed $261 million, losing $123
million, making it one of the biggest box-office bombs of all time.
The film explores themes of helicopter, mexico city, mexico,
artificial intelligence (a.i.), cyborg, dystopia.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.